shabugames.com 2009-02-20

# Shabu Games - Privacy Policies

Shabu Games created this privacy policy to show our commitment to privacy issues. The content below describes our privacy practices.

**Third-Party Web Beacons**

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [ click here](https://ondemand.indextools.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=stats.indextools.com)."

**Anonymous information**

Anonymous information refers to data that cannot be referred back to a specific individual. We collect the visitor's IP address, referral stats, and browser and platform type. And you do not have to sign up with Shabu Games before we can collect this anonymous information. 

**Personal Information**

We respect customers' privacy. We do not collect personal information unless you give it to us when downloading or ordering a game or signing up for a free email newsletter. No personal information given to us is used for any other  purpose other than what is stated in this policy. We send emails to subscribers to inform about new games and useful information about games.

We do not sell, distribute, share, or give your information to any other company for any marketing or sale purposes. 

our email information is used solely by Shabu Games through our Newsletter and for adding users to ShabuGames's My Big Fish Games friends list and emails relating to the My Big Fish Games affiliate program.

If you don't want to receive any email from us, you can opt-out from the mailing list at any time. 

**Cookies**   
We do not use cookies on this site. But we use third-party e-commerce companies (RegNow, Big Fish Games, Reflexive Games) to track download/purchase on this site. All these e-commerce companies are well established in the market. Cookies are used on many game download links to track referrals from this site. All full version purchases made from these downloads are then credited to Shabu Games from game developer partners on a revenue sharing basis. 

**External Links**

This site links to other websites. Shabu Games is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites that we are linking to.

**Copyright & Trademarks **Microsoft, DirectX, DirectSound and Windows are either registered or trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries. Intel and Pentium are registered trademarks of Intel Corporation. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owner.

Shabu Games reserves the right to change this privacy policy from time to time.
